RAY : I think he 's dead .
[ GIRL SCREAMS ]
BARRY : don 't ever , under any circumstances known to god ,
speak about this again .
Julie : What are you waiting for ?
Ben Willis : if you leave a man for dead , make sure he 's really dead .
[ SCREAMS ]
[ THUNDER CLAPS ]
Bless me , father , for I have sinned .
It 's been a year since my last confession .
I 've never told anyone this .
Not my mom , not the police , not even my friends .
Except for the ones who were there and ...
Well , they 're not around anymore .
You see , I ...
Yes ?
I killed a man .
But it was an accident ,
a terrible accident .
And I 've tried to get past it , but I can 't .
Go on .
I have these ... Dreams ,
Really horrible dreams .
This man is always there with me .
He was a killer .
He murdered Barry and Helen , and he would 've killed me too ,
but I got away with it .
Oh , I guess I just need to deal with it , you know ?
Face the fear and the guilt .
Finally say his name .
Ben Willis .
- Ben Willis . - I know .
You know ? How could you ?
I know what you did last summer .
[ SCREAMS ]
It 's nice to see you find political science so stimulating , Miss James .
I 'm sorry .
- Julie , wait . You okay ? - I 'm fine .
- You sure ? - Yeah , I 'm fine .
- You don 't seem fine . - I had another dream , Will .
- The one in the shower ? - No , in the church .
God , it was so real .
- I mean , I could feel his breath on me . - I 'm sorry .
And I thought that the dreams were over .
I mean , I hadn 't had one for months .
- It takes time , Julie . It 'll get better . - Well , it can 't get much worse .
That 's not the first time that I freaked out in class , Will .
I mean , I can 't study . I don 't get any sleep .
And I am this close - this close to failing school .
[ BANGS ]
[ SCREAMS ]
BOY : Happy fourth of July !
[ BOYS LAUGH ]
It was one year ago .
It 's the anniversary . That 's what it is .
You just gotta take it easy on yourself .
Well , I 'm really trying , Will but you know What
But sometimes I wonder why I even came up here In the first place .
- To get out of Southport . - Right . Now I remember .
So , are you getting out of town for the fourth ?
No , I 'll probably just be here studying for finals .
- The joys of summer school . - Right .
- Are you okay ? - I 'm fine .
- You sure ? - Yes .
- You 're definitely okay ? - Yes , I am definitely okay .
Look , thanks for the talk , Will .
- You 're good to me , you know that ? - I am ?
Yeah .
Um , okay . I 'll see you later .
Okay . Bye .
- Julie . - Ray !
Hi . But ... God , what are you doing here ?
I got in early .
- Uh , who was that guy ? - Oh , that 's Will . He 's a friend .
- You 'd like him . - Yeah .
Ray , we 're just friends .
Every guy in history who tried to pick up on a girl
did the " good friend " thing first .
Are you ready to go ? I got my truck .
You know the drill . There 's a crab boil at Ollie 's .
It 's a croaker queen pageant .
It 's small-town fun , but it 's still nice .
Ray , I can 't .
You can 't what ?
I just feel like there 's this small part of me
that hasn 't healed up enough to go back .
- So please understand . - Yeah , I understand .
It 's not like that , Ray . It 's not you .
Okay , it is not you . It 's all me . In my head .
I wanna go back . I wanna be fine . I wanna be with you .
And I want everything to be like it was . It just isn 't .
Why don 't you stay up here ?
Fireworks over the river , a million little things to do .
I have to work , Julie .
My boat 's in Southport , remember ?
But , hey , it 's cool .
You need your space from croakerland and ...
Probably from me too .
Ray .
Just forget it .
Ray !
I 'm scared , that 's all .
BOYS : First down ! here we go ! Go ! Go !
♪ Did you ever think of me ♪
♪ As a best friend ♪
♪ Did I ever think of you ♪
♪ I 'm not complaining ♪
♪ I never try to feel ♪
♪ this vibration ♪
♪ I never try to reach ♪
♪ your Eden ♪
[ DOOR CLICKS ]
Shit !
[ FLOORBOARDS CREAK ]
[ SCREAMS ]
- What are you doing in my closet ? - I thought you were out of town .
What the hell are you doing in my closet ?
Julie , I thought you were out of town .
I just wanted to borrow your black skirt , but I 'm not ready to die for it .
Jesus , Karla , that was like heart attack time .
Can I have the knife now , please ?
I think you should come out with me tonight .
Well , I don 't think so .
I just tried to stab you with a knife , Karla .
I hardly feel like dancing .
What 's the matter ?
- I think I just hurt Ray 's feelings . - Julie .
Listen to me , okay , Ray is a great guy .
Nothing against old Ray , but he 's so ... Ray .
I mean , he lives in Southport , Julie .
Will 's a nice guy and he lives right down the street .
Yeah , but there 's nothing between Will and me .
Yet . Nothing yet .
You know what ? We gotta keep moving too .
Now , I 'm working at the club tonight .
- You , dancing queen , are coming with me . - No , I 'm not .
- Yes , you are . - No , I 'm not .
What did I say ?
[ RAVE MUSIC ]
Now , you know what I want to do to you , right ? Right ? Huh ?
No , I 'm not aware of that .
There 's gotta be a place in here where we can be alone .
Baby , you know what , I don 't think so . It 's pretty crowded in here .
Come on baby , don 't be like that .
I just wanna talk to you for a minute .
If you can say all you have to say to me in one minute , then I don 't wanna hear it .
- Hey , I 'll talk real , real slow . - Not at work .
You know what ? Do me a favor . Ask Julie to dance .
You know , Jules , you 're the most beautiful woman in the bar tonight .
You know , Ty , you are an unstoppable force of nature .
You better recognize . See , that 's how my species survives .
You 'll never convince me otherwise .
- What 's up ? Wanna dance ? - Say yes .
- No . - No means yes . Don 't listen to her .
Ty , I really appreciate it , but have you seen my people dance ?
We do the mouth thing , snap the fingers .
Hey , if worse come to worse , you can just stand there and watch me .
You know what , I have an idea .
Why don 't we all take a break and we can go dance ?
Come on . Let 's go . You know it .
Ooh , what do you know ? Will Benson , looking fine .
Karla , did you tell him I was gonna be here ?
No , I told him that you would absolutely not be at this bar
between 10 : 00 and 11 : 00 and then he came anyway .
- Hi , will . What 's up ? - This wasn 't my idea .
- What ? - I said this wasn 't my idea .
- Come on . Let 's go . - Hey , you 'll be fine . Do your thing .
KARLA : Be good , Julie . You wanna get a drink ?
- Yeah . - Okay .
Go , Ty . Go , Ty .
Hey .
You see something back there ?
Yeah . You know what , I 'm really sorry , Will , but I 've gotta go home right now .
I 'm really sorry .
[ CLANGING ]
Morning .
[ SIGHS ]
Ooh , I love when they do that .
Okay , that could break the machine .
Oh please , Julie .
[ PHONE RINGS ]
Ooh , that 's Ty . Thanks .
- My number 's unlisted . - Julie , will you relax ?
We 've been dating for three months and he is not a stalker .
Hi , Ty .
This is Mark in the Morning from Magic 96.7 radio station .
- Who am I speaking with ? - Oh , my god , Julie !
It 's Mark in the Morning ! Oh my god !
Okay , um , put on the speakerphone .
Oh , my god ! mark in the morning !
Hi , Mark . Um , I 'm Karla . Karla Wilson .
Well , Karla , what are you doing at home on the long fourth of July weekend ?
Uh , well , um , I 'm actually in school studying really hard .
How would you like to win a Magic 96.7 quickie getaway ?
Hell , yeah !
I hope you remember your geography , Karla ... because all you have to do to win
is tell me the capital of Brazil .
- Okay , Brazil . The capital of Brazil ... - Come on , Karla .
One easy question , one great getaway .
Karla , we need an answer .
No looking it up . Okay , Karla , five seconds .
Five seconds . Four .
- Rio . Rio . Rio . - Three .
Two . Okay . Uh , Rio de Janeiro !
- Oh , no . Did you say Rio ? - No .
Yes ? Yes !
You just won Magic 96.7 's quickie getaway .
A trip for four to Tower Bay island in the fabulous Bahamas !
Okay , shut up . I can 't hear . Okay , hello ?
We 'll call you back with all the details . So what 's your favorite radio station ?
- Magic 96.7 ! Magic 96.7 ! - That 's what I thought .
[ JOYFUL SCREECHING ]
Okay , okay . Who am I gonna take ? Let 's see , Tyrell .
- Wait a second . Me , me , me , me . - My parents , cousins . Okay , Julie .
You know what , Mark said four tickets , so you have to think of someone to bring .
♪ How do I deal with you ♪
♪ How do I deal with me ♪
Hey , Ray ! Phone !
♪ What it is you want from me ♪
♪ And how do I deal with love ? ♪
♪ How do I know what 's real ? ♪
- Yeah ? - Julie : Hi .
Hey . I 'm really glad you called .
- I 'm sorry . - No , you shouldn 't be sorry .
I shouldn 't have left so fast , I just ...
Ray , listen .
Karla just won a trip to the Bahamas .
Um , this island called Tower Bay .
And she wants us to go with her .
The Bahamas . Really ?
It would be a great chance for us to just hang out for the weekend .
You know , just kind of sitting in the sun , drinking fruity drinks , swimming and ...
And , well ... [ GROWLS ]
You know .
Wait . This weekend ?
Yeah .
So you can go away with your college friends , but you can 't go away with me ?
Ray , it 's not you . It 's Southport .
And , god , it 's the Bahamas . You know , free .
Damn , you have to sell his ass on the Bahamas ?
Ray , listen , I really want us to be together .
Julie , listen .
We 're in the middle of a really big run up here .
And it 's been crazy .
I think we gotta go back out again tonight .
I don 't think I could make it up .
Will you try , for me , please ?
Yeah , I 'll try , but ...
Listen .
If I don 't make it up , then you go ahead .
Have a really great time .
Ray , for me , try , please . I really miss you .
I miss you too .
Okay . Um ...
Bye .
[ FISHERMEN BANTER ]
Dude , what is your problem ?
You haven 't caught dick for days , man .
Pull that big ugly shit out of your ass , she asked you to go to the Bahamas .
Fuck it man , you gotta go .
Hey man , I 'll ride up with you , kick it with my homies in Cambridge .
Yeah . Stupid .
Yeah , stupid .
What were you thinking , man ?
I 'll show you what I 've been thinking .
Whoa . Ray ! damn !
Thanks , but I 'll need a little time to think about it .
- Nice fit , huh ? - Yeah ..
Listen , I should call Julie back , tell her I 'm coming .
No way , man . Surprise her , she 'll be psyched .
Yeah . Yeah .
All right , clean up .
Julie , would you please forget about Ray ?
That boy has got fish on the brains . Okay ?
Yeah , but ...
But nothing . Where are we going ?
- The Bahamas . - Where we going ?
Where are we going , Julie ?
BOTH : The Bahamas !
♪ Here I go again on my own ♪
♪ Going down the only road I 've ever known ♪
- Hey , try the harmony . - You try the harmony , man . I 'll lead .
You 're gonna lead ? Dude , you suck .
Fuck you man , I sound just like the dude .
Listen , listen .
♪ And I 've made up my mind ♪
Yo , you don 't sound anything like that guy .
- Are you deaf ? - Fuck you .
I 'm quitting this band , man .
I 'm going solo .
[ LAUGHS ]
Oh shit .
What are you doing , man , just keep going .
- Find a phone . - No .
Come on . The guy looks dead , man .
Maybe not .
What are you doing , man ?
[ DOOR SLAMS ]
This is fucked up , man .
Shit .
[ DEEP BREATH ]
Dave !
[ SCREAMS ]
No !
[ WHEELS SCREECH ]
[ HORN HONKS ]
[ BRAKES SCREECH ]
[ RAY GROANS ]
Girl , it 's getting down to the wire .
- He 's not coming . - No .
I just thought ...
Julie , you left him four messages .
Four messages .
He said he 'd try .
Try is like maybe , Julie . Try is bullshit .
Bullshit .
- He does work hard . - Work hard , my ass .
Julie , he 's only breaking your heart because he can .
And I don 't wanna be the one to say I told you so .
Then don 't .
[ TIRES SCREECH ]
Oh , my god .
What 's happenin ' , lovers ? What 's going on ?
We gonna get tropical or we gonna get tropical , huh ?
Let me talk to you for a minute ...
- What 's up , Jules ? - Hi .
Julie , Julie , please , I 'm really sorry about Will .
But I mean he 's my friend too ,
and I didn 't want my ticket to go to waste .
So , where there 's a Will , there 's a way .
So , let 's start having fun now .
Come on . Whoo !
What 's up ? Is there a problem ?
No . No , there is no problem ...
because we are all going to the Bahamas .
- You damn right . - Right .
We are going to the Bahamas .
To the Bahamas .
♪ Don 't you know ♪
♪ It 's not really that complicated ♪
♪ Hey , now , now ♪
WILL : ' pull , emergency ' ... I 'm in the wrong row .
- I shouldn 't be in this row . - Are you okay ?
Yeah , I 'm fine .
[ TURBULENCE ]
- Ooh ! - Um , you know what ? Take deep breaths .
Think of something happy from your childhood .
What if I don 't have anything happy from childhood ?
I 'm sorry , I just can 't relax going 500 miles an hour .
- Deep breaths . - Fumes build up in the fuel tanks .
You can buy surface to air missiles over the internet .
Planes fall out of the sky for practically no reason at all .
You 'd have a better chance of getting hit by lightning .
Planes get hit by lightning . They get hit by meteors .
- They hit other planes . - TY : You 're gonna get hit all right ...
if you don 't quit bitchin ' .
- Deep breaths . - Some folks just can 't fly .
KARLA : I 'm the king of the world !
JULIE : King of the world !
[ VOMITS ]
- Just breathe , Tyrell . Breathe . - Man , get away from me , man .
See , it 's not a macho thing .
It 's about equilibrium in your inner ear .
I mean , you could have used the patch but it 's too late now .
You 've just gotta get used to it .
Some folks just can 't sail .
Too bad too , ' cause it 's the only way on or off the island .
Unless you have an accident , then they call the coast guard .
Well , it looks pretty remote , doesn 't it ?
Yeah , but that 's what the tourists pay for : sun , sea and solitude .
- Hey , how much longer , man ? - A few more minutes , kid .
Hang in there .
Don 't hold back . Let it out .
Just watch the boat , that way .
♪ One of these faces doesn 't belong here ♪
♪ Hey , look at that girl ♪
♪ I just don 't belong here ♪
REP : Ladies , if there 's anything I can do
to make your stay more pleasurable here ,
please don 't hesitate to ask .
My name is Darrick , and I will be at your service
for the duration of your stay , ladies .
" Duration of your stay , ladies . "
Listen , old man , I gotta work fast .
The season 's almost over .
If the radio 's right about the weather , you 're already out of time .
Old man , my ass .
♪ I just don 't belong here ♪
♪ Hey , look at that girl ♪
[ BOAT ENGINE SOUNDS ]
Beautiful .
- Oh , wow . - Look at this .
TY : Oh , we are here . We have arrived in paradise !
Psst ! Hey !
You gotta be shitting me .
Look at this cat .
Yo , what 's up , my brother ?
Hey , Tyrell , I think we found your brother .
I think we found your brother .
Damn ! you know what I was saying ?
Are you looking for some bud ? Shh .
I got some bat guano . I got the cream jeans .
Listen , anything you guys need , Titus got .
No , thank you , but thank you very much .
What 's up ? Everybody needs something .
What about the ladies , the sweet young ladies ?
- Is there anything I can do ? - Take a bath .
Oh , damn , that 's cold , woman ! All right .
Listen , if you need some weed , I 'll get with you later .
Hey , what 's up ?
- Was you looking for the disco ? - Beat it .
♪ Hey , look at that girl ♪
♪ I just don 't belong here ♪
[ CHATTER ]
[ BELL RINGS ]
KARLA : Hello ?
[ RINGING CONTINUES ]
Hello ?
- Yoo-hoo ! - God , where is everyone ?
That 's a good question .
Oh , excuse me .
Excuse me .
TY : I 'll scare somebody up .
Hello .
[ DOG BARKS ]
- Shit ! - Aagh !
[ BELL RINGS ]
What can I do for you ?
Checking in . Karla Wilson .
Oh , yes , well , let 's roll out the red carpet .
Our contest winners are finally here .
Last name first , first name last .
Nice dog you got there , man .
Not really .
Found pieces of guys like you in his stool .
You got a problem with something ?
I don 't have a problem in the world , pal .
You know what , this is such a beautiful old hotel .
Don 't you think ?
It was built in the 19303 for one of the Rockefeller clan .
Tiles are imported from Spain . There 's a lot of history here .
Judy Garland spent the night here , President Nixon ...
Okay , okay , okay . We understand , we get it , it 's old .
It 'll outlive you , I 'm sure .
- Put that down , please . - Oh . Sorry .
Wilson .
Comma . Karla .
- Oh . - Oh , what ?
- You 're in 201 and 202 . - Is that a bad thing ?
No . Not at all .
Not at all .
Those are our honeymoon suites .
- Your what ? - Honeymoon suite .
I take it you kids haven 't exchanged vows , have you ?
- We haven 't exchanged anything . - KARLA : Julie , come on .
We 're talking suites .
That 'll be fine with us .
During your stay , our marginally trained off-season staff of five
will tend to your every need .
Wait a minute , did you say off-season ?
Hmm ? It 's the fourth of July weekend .
Storm season begins today . Clouds roll in like clockwork .
- Storm season ? - Yes , it 's our version of winter .
[ BELL RINGS ]
That 's 201 and 202 .
Scrabble and Parcheesi in the lounge .
Enjoy .
KARA : Ain 't nothing free in this world . Everybody says it , and it 's true .
- I wanted you guys to have a great trip . - Aw , baby , we will .
Don 't even worry about that .
We got the whole island to ourselves , all right ?
WILL : Plus , Karla , it 's been blue skies all day .
It might be perfect all weekend .
Oh , guys , this is us . 202 .
TY : The bags .
201 and 202 .
- Don 't use these much . - Really ? Why is that ?
No reason in particular .
It 's just that these are fancy rooms for kids your age .
KARLA : Yeah , well , we won a competition .
Oh . And what did you have to do ?
- Guess the capital of Brazil . - Rio , baby .
- That 's right . - Ah .
Good for you , girl .
And , uh , where would you like I put your bags ?
Oh , you can put their stuff in there and , urn , ours back here .
Karla , you promised .
And I also promised Tyrell .
Julie , what 's up , man ? You killing me .
Julie , look , if it 's cool I can sleep on the couch .
That way they can have the same room and practice that real honeymoon .
- I 'll take those . - No . No .
I 've been doing this since before you were a gleam in your father 's eye .
You sure it 's cool with you ?
Yeah , sure . As long as you promise not to snore .
If I get out of hand , you can toss something at me .
[ LAUGHS ]
[ BEEPS ]
MAN : He looks pretty beat up .
Yeah . But he seems certain .
His friend was killed out on the highway by somebody named Ben Willis .
He said this Willis guy had a hook on his hand and was driving a BMW .
Look , there 's no body . There 's no other vehicle involved .
He fell asleep at the wheel .
He crashed his truck into a guardrail .
He got thrown a hell of a long way down into a ditch , and he 's damn lucky .
Well , he suffered severe head trauma .
Well , after he rests up , it 'll probably all come back to him .
[ LONG BEEP ]
Doctor , number three just flatlined .
Get me some help up here . I 've got a flatline , room three .
TANNOY : Code blue ICU Three .
Code blue ICU Three .
[ OCEAN SOUNDS ]
TY : You need a couple of drinks , it 'll be good , you know what I 'm saying ?
Oh shit .
- This bar is , um ... - Empty ?
WOMAN : You boys lost ?
TY : Oh , wow , a human being .
Uh , please , just tell me this isn 't the bar scene .
- You want a drink ? - We didn 't get all dressed up for nothing .
- Oh , you 're dressed up ? - Ahh !
All right , Will . Check this out , man .
All right , we got a planter 's punch .
We got a Singapore sling .
How about a Mai mother-fucking Thai ?
- Mai mother-fucking Thai . - Yeah .
How about some I.D. ?
I 'm kidding .
[ BREATHY LAUGH ]
The guy at the desk said the place would be quiet , not dead .
Yeah , well , I guess he didn 't tell you that this is ...
The last day of the season . Yes , he told us .
So , why are you still here ?
That 's none of your god damned business .
- I think I smell man trouble . - Yeah .
No . No , not anymore .
Did he dump you ?
No . I shot him .
Now , what you boys want ...
is a Dark and Stormy , a little Vernon 's rum with ginger beer , a splash of Tabasco .
It 's good , trust me .
Am I bad ?
I mean , he 's really great , right , and kind of cute ?
Yes , he is cute and he has a crush on you .
But I miss Ray . I really do , you know ?
I tried to call him .
You know what , Julie ? Ray made up his own mind .
So that means you 're free to make up yours .
So for the next 48 hours , your smile is a frown turned upside down .
Oh , really ?
Here comes my baby .
Hi . You like the outfit ? No . I love it .
- Oh , thank you . - What y 'all think ?
It 's a pretty cool bar , right ?
Every one starts to look the same once you 've worked in one .
- Am I right , sister ? - Got that right .
You look beautiful .
- I 'm Julie . This is Karla . - Nancy . - Hi .
Well , welcome to Tower Bay 's most happening hot spot .
Up in our room is going to be the most happening hot spot .
- NANCY : Okay . Four dark and stormies . - Drinks is here .
All right , to a great weekend .
- To a great weekend . - Screw the weather !
- Hmm ... - Mmm .
So , what do you do around here for fun ?
Make fun of tourists , basically .
Or let them make fun of themselves .
Ooh , karaoke . Perfect .
Now , that 's what I 'm talking about right there .
- No . Don 't even think about it . - Okay , I won 't .
Don 't even listen to them party poopers . You keep doing your thing .
No , baby . This is not for me . This is for someone who really needs it .
So , one singer with extra cheese .
Karla , no .
- Yes , Julie . - No .
- Yes . - No .
What did I say ?
Come on , Julie . Come on , come on .
Don 't you people listen to me ?
- Julie in the house ! - Let 's do it !
Ladies and gentlemen , please give a round of applause ...
for my friend , my very best friend - get up here .
- Julie James ! - Julie James ! Julie !
Julie James in the house .
TY AND WILL : Julie ! Julie !
[ CHANTING ' JULIE ' ]
All right .
[ PIANO PLAYS ]
- Thank you , Karla . - You 're welcome .
♪ At first I was afraid I was petrified ♪
♪ Kept thinkin ' I could never live without you by my side ♪
Are you happy ?
♪ Then I spent so many nights thinkin ' how you did me wrong ♪
♪ And I grew strong ♪
♪ And I learned how to get along ♪
♪ But now you 're back from outer space ♪
Hi , Will .
♪ I just walked in to find you here with that sad look upon your face ♪
♪ I should 've changed that stupid look ♪
♪ I should 've made you leave the key ♪
♪ If I had known for just one second you 'd be back to bother me ♪
♪ Oh , now go ♪
Everyone 's a god damned singer .
♪ Just turn around now ' cause you 're not welcome anymore ♪
I don 't know the lyrics . Hold on .
[ LAUGHS ]
It 's him .
WILL : What do you mean ?
He did something to the screen , I swear to god .
What 's up with the music ?
- Julie , what 's wrong ? - I swear to god , it said ...
WILL : What do you mean ?
Julie , what are you talking about ?
- Nothing . - TY : What 's the matter ?
- Where are you going ? - Julie !
[ RUNNING FOOTSTEPS ]
Shit .
[ SIGHS ]
[ SCREAMS ]
[ SMASH ]
- Oh , my god ! - It 's my fault .
- Will , I am so sorry . - It 's my fault .
- I shouldn 't have ... I didn 't think . - No , it was ...
- This is so sweet . I 'm sorry . - Oh .
I scared you . I crossed the line .
No , you scared me , but I 'm a little on edge .
- Sorry . - Hey , you don 't have to apologize .
I 'm ... I 'm the one . I understand .
I 'm , uh ...
I 'm just gonna take a walk .
Are you sure ?
- Hmm ? - Yeah .
[ GLASS CHINKS ]
I just really like you a lot , you know .
I want you to have a great time .
I want you to be happy .
Um , I 'll just grab a few things here .
Oh , god , I 'm sorry .
[ DOOR CLICKS ]
I 'm sorry .
[ KARLA MOANS , BED SQUEAKS ]
[ MOANS ]
- Bounce , baby , bounce . - Baby , you know what ?
What ?
I 've decided , I 'm gonna change my major to finance .
And I 'm going to Wall Street .
- You know why ? - Why is that , lover ?
Because it 's the only way I can afford a big-ass bed like this .
Why don 't you show me some love on this big-ass bed ?
Ooh ! A Jacuzzi .
Come on , baby , don 't go over there . Let 's stay right here .
Baby , I spent a hundred bucks on my new bathing suit .
And even if it 's just for you to pull it off , I gotta wear it .
That 's what I 'm talking about .
You didn 't mention that earlier , you sexy thing .
[ WAVES LAP ]
[ WHISTLES ]
[ CREAKS ]
[ SIGHS ]
[ VOCAL SOUND ]
[ QUIET SMASH ]
[ SCREAMS ]
[ CRAZED NOISES ]
[ LAUGHS ]
Damn it , man . You scared the shit out of me .
You 're living your life in fear , bro .
It 's time for your passage into manhood .
What do you want , Titus ?
Okay , hear me out .
There 's a kick-ass party on the mainland .
I 'm saying we take the boat and get jiggy with it .
- No . - Aw , come on , man .
I gotta tie the boat , there 's a storm coming .
Then I 'm going to bed .
- And that 's it ? - That 's all I got for today , man .
- Please , take the bake elsewhere . - All right .
Be careful , please .
Listen , buddy . You need to take a chill pill .
- Have a good time , bro . - I will , buddy .
[ STRAINS ]
[ ROPE SCRAPES ]
[ GRUNTS ]
Titus !
Oh , damn it !
Very funny , asshole .
[ GROANS ]
Hey , man , give me a hand , would you ?
[ SCREAMS ]
[ SPLASH ]
[ PUFFS ]
[ SIGHS ]
[ DIAL TONES ]
[ PHONE RINGS ]
- Long distance . - I need an international operator .
One moment , please .
[ PHONE RINGS ]
[ RINGING CONTINUES ]
Come on .
[ KNOCKS ]
Housekeeping .
[ DOOR CLICKS ]
[ KNOCKS ]
Housekeeping .
[ SOFT FOOTSTEPS ]
[ SCREAMS ]
[ SLASH ]
[ THUD ]
[ DOOR SLAMS ]
[ GENTLE WATER SOUNDS ]
What ? What ? What ?
You seen my hair tie ?
Oh , come on .
I 'm sorry , baby . I just don 't wanna get my hair wet .
[ SIGHS ]
I finally got you alone in this Jacuzzi ,
and , personally , I do not wanna be talking about hair care .
- Don 't get feisty . - Feisty ?
It 's too late for all that .
' Cause you know what ?
We 're miles away from anybody .
So nobody can hear you scream .
Mmm , well I used to be a lifeguard .
And , please , don 't make me blow my whistle .
Oh , I 'd just hate ...
for you to blow your whistle .
[ YELLS ]
Shit !
No water sports after midnight .
That 's hotel policy .
Oh yeah , then what 's the policy on burning ' erb ?
You can 't try it until you buy it .
[ VOICE STRAINS ]
- What 's up ? - Hey !
Oh , it 's all good .
And believe me , it is all good .
Crazy freak .
[ TITUS LAUGHS ]
Now , where was I ?
WILL : Hey , guys . Isn 't this beautiful ?
- Damn . - Oh , come on .
TY : You 're killing me . There 's ten people on this whole island ,
and they 're all going to end up in this Jacuzzi .
- How 's the water ? - Crowded .
This feels great .
Will , how 's Julie doing ?
She 's up in her room alone .
- Any advice ? - Yeah . Find another Jacuzzi .
Will , you can 't give up so easy , you gotta hang in there .
It 's great , isn 't it ?
I can 't win .
- I can 't . - Oh ...
[ SHOWER SPRAYS ]
[ WATER STOPS ]
[ THUD ]
Will ?
[ DOOR CLICKS ]
[ MIRROR SQUEAKS ]
Now , where in the hell 's my toothbrush ?
[ CLICKS ]
[ CREAKS ]
[ HEAVY BREATHING ]
[ SCREAMS ]
I know , I know , I know ...
JULIE : Will !
Will ! It 's happening again !
What ? What happened ?
I do not find this at all funny .
There ... there was a body in there , I swear it .
Julie , you said you were tired . Maybe you were dreaming .
No , I wasn 't dreaming .
I knew you people were gonna be trouble .
I knew it the moment I laid eyes on you .
- No , you listen to me , he 's here . - Who ? Who 's here ?
- NANCY : Hey , what 's going on ?
I don 't know , Julie 's talking about she saw some dead guy in the closet
but all we see is bathrobes .
Cool .
Ty , do you think this is funny ?
Damn it , Tyrell , I am not going crazy , he was in there .
Oh , yeah ? Then where is he now , Julie ?
Huh ? Where 's the dead guy ?
Julie , think about it , okay , I mean what did you actually see ?
I saw the dock hand guy hanging by his neck in there .
All right , look .
In the morning , we 'll talk to Darrick , the dock hand guy ,
and we 'll put this whole thing to rest .
In the meantime , let 's slow down on the dark and stormies and get some sleep .
- Don 't look at me . - No , I want off this island .
That 's not possible .
I 'm afraid the last ferry left a couple of hours ago
There won 't be another one for days .
We have a storm coming .
Fine . Then I 'll call the mainland and I 'll get a boat .
Phones went down a few minutes ago .
[ PHONE RATTLES ]
It 's dead .
[ THUNDER RUMBLES ]
Duh . Now , listen up .
The next couple of days are going to be rough ... but we 'll make it .
- What about a radio ? - Emergencies only .
- What would you call this ? - I 'd call this four spoiled city kids
who wouldn 't know a hurricane if it blew up their ass .
Look , this is not a drill .
All we can do now is batten down and ride it out .
And if it gets really bad , we have a storm shelter .
Good night .
[ THUNDER CLAPS ]
[ BIRDS FLAP ]
[ RAIN POURS ]
[ TRINKETS CHIME ]
The pain of the past , the fear of the future ,
the blood of the young .
[ CHUCKLES ]
Yeah , that 's my babies .
Y 'all growed up good .
Y 'all growed up real good .
[ REGGAE MUSIC ]
Now , where you hiding in ?
Come to papa .
Yeah .
That 's it .
Gotta find that damn lighter .
[ FOOTSTEPS ]
Can I help you ?
[ HOOK SWIPES ]
[ SCREAMS ]
God damn it ! Aagh !
[ CRAZED CRYING ]
Oh god !
What are you doing ?
No .
Seriously , don 't do that !
Oh , god , I ... Jesus , no !
No ! it 's all good !
No !
[ SLASH ]
MAN : Hey , over here !
[ STREET CHATTER ]
[ DOORBELL RINGS ]
[ TV PLAYS ]
Can I help you ?
[ DISTANT SIRENS ]
[ SCOFFS ]
- That 's a full carat . - How much ?
- Well , she 's got some pilkes in her . - How much ?
Tell you the truth , I don 't have much of a market for this kind of thing .
- Best I can do is ... two , maybe 250 . - Make it 300 .
And throw in that too .
Which one are we talking about ?
You 're crazy , boy .
That 's worth 300 all by itself .
- Then there 's a waitin ' period . - I 'm not waitin ' !
So keep the ring , and give me the gun .
[ UNLOCKS CASE ]
Look , boy , you sure you want to go this way ?
- Is it loaded ? - No .
Load it .
[ RAIN POURS ]
[ THUNDER CLAPS ]
Will , get the hell off me , man .
Baby , I gotta tell you , this is bullshit !
This ain 't the romantic weekend I had in mind , you know ?
Hey , Jules .
Get any sleep ?
Yeah , some .
TY : Wow , look at that .
Another beautiful day in paradise , with Julie as our tour director .
" Miss Psychotic Episode . "
Hey , Julie , you see any dead bodies out there ?
Any fresh kill ?
- KARLA : Shut up , Ty . - How ' bout a Freddie
- or a Jason or somebody ? - WILL : Why don 't you leave her alone ?
' Cause I 'm just tellin ' y 'all what everybody is thinkin ' .
It 's bad enough gettin ' rained out
without having to hold her hand the whole damn time .
But you don 't have to be an asshole about it .
No , it 's okay .
It 's okay , he doesn 't believe me .
That 's his right , I 'm starting to think I 'm crazy too .
- Julie , nobody thinks you 're crazy , okay ? - I do .
You know what , why don 't you guys go find something to do ?
Baby , I don 't wanna do nothin ' with him . I wanna do somethin ' with you .
- Please . - [ TUTS ]
Why don 't we go to the gym and work off some of that stress ?
[ CHUCKLES ]
Nobody thinks you 're crazy .
[ TUTS ]
[ RAIN POURS ]
Look , this is what we need to do . We need to find " stoner boy , "
make his stupid ass hook us up with some ping-pong paddles
- or pool sticks or somethin ' . - You know what ?
The greenhouse effect has caused the gulf stream to shift ,
and almost every meteorological expert
expects some dramatic increase in tropical depression ,
which cause hurricanes and massive coastal flooding .
It wouldn 't take much of a storm surge to wipe us right off of this island .
Hey , hey , hey , hey .
Shut up , okay ? Shut up !
God !
Come on !
This is a nice gym .
[ grunts ]
Wow ! Nice move .
Yeah . I 'm gonna give your fisherman ...
some of this and see how he likes it .
[ PANTS ]
[ TREADMILL BEEPS ]
Oh , poor baby .
You know what , Julie ? I got a better idea .
You 're not leaving this island till you get a tan . Come on .
JULIE : Wow . Cancer in a box .
KARLA : Nah , this is the safe sun .
[ LAUGHS ]
Come on , Julie . It 's better than a day on the beach , girl .
[ DIAL CLICKS ]
Here we go .
With a little photosynthesis , you will feel like a new ...
- Houseplant ? - Exactly . Bye .
Bye .
[ DOOR CLICKS ]
[ SIGHS ]
[ RAIN POURS ]
[ PANTS ]
WILL : You 're sure this is the way to the pool ?
TY : Well , there 's his cart .
Fucking idiot left it in the rain .
[ GRUNTS ]
[ CLATTERING ]
[ CLATTERING CONTINUES ]
Oh , the dryer .
Gee Karla , that 'll break the machine .
Damn , how many pairs is in there ?
[ DOOR SQUEAKS ]
[ SCREAMS ]
WILL : Hey , pool boy !
TY : Yo , Bob Marley !
You in there ? Hey , you in there or what ?
[ HEADPHONES MUSIC ]
[ THUDDING FOOTSTEPS ]
[ HOOK CHINKS ]
[ HEADPHONES MUSIC ]
[ MACHINE BUZZES ]
Karla ?
[ BANGS DOOR ]
Karla !
[ SCREAMS ]
[ HYSTERICAL SCREAMS ]
[ CRASH ]
Come on !
[ JULIE SCREAMS ]
Julie ! it 's Julie !
[ SCREAMS ]
Oh , Tyrell !
[ STRAINS ]
You guys , help me ! Will !
We have to cut it .
[ SCREAMS ]
- Use this ! just smash it ! - No , come back !
[ ELECTRICITY CRACKLES ]
[ SCREAMS ]
See , I 'm not crazy ! I told you I was not crazy !
He 's here ! We 've got to get to a radio and call for help !
Man , this classifies as a fucking emergency .
Hey , Brooks ! Where you fucking at , man ?
Huh ? We want off this island !
Oh shit .
We got to get the fuck out of here .
[ STATIC ]
Julie ?
Julie !
KARLA : Where are the boats ?
There were boats here !
TY : They were cut loose !
WILL : Julie , you want to tell us what the fuck is going on here ?
We 're all gonna die ! He 's gonna kill us one by one !
- Who ? - Ben Willis .
Oh , fuck this shit !
You 've gotta forget that shit , alright ? Ben Willis is dead ,
- you killed him , remember ? - They never found the body .
Two summers ago , we lied to the authorities .
We hit Ben Willis with our car ,
and then we threw his body in the water to cover it up ,
only he didn 't die .
He killed Barry and Helen last July 4th .
I swear I thought Ray and I had killed him , but we didn 't .
- Get the hell out of here ! - No ! You listen to me !
- He 's back to finish it off ! - Julie , we are in the middle of nowhere !
There 's dead bodies piling up all over the place !
And as far as I can see , there 's only one guy missing !
- The porter ! The porter ! What 's his name ? - Estes !
That 's exactly who it is ! I 'm telling you , that fucker know something .
Now , we can sit here like assholes and wait for him to pick us off ,
- or we can go find him first . - It 's not him .
Fuck that , we 've got to do somethin ' .
I 'm with him .
- Come on ! - Julie , I can 't believe you .
How can you not tell me the whole story ?
I 'm your best friend !
I just wanted it to be over . I didn 't want to involve anybody else .
Well , it 's too late for that now .
TY : Come on , let 's go !
[ ENGINE REVS ]
[ SIGHS ]
TY : Hey , Estes !
Hey , you sick bastard !
You in here , huh ?
Fuck . You hear me ?
Sick motherfu ...
- He 's not here , man . - There 's some crazy stuff in here , man !
[ TY PANTS ]
[ TRINKETS JINGLE ]
Oh yeah , no doubt .
This is our fucking killer .
This is our fucking guy .
[ SKULL THUDS ]
[ CLINKS AND JANGLES ]
[ DOOR CREAKS ]
You guys !
[ TY PANTS ]
- Anyone missing a hair tie ? - That 's mine .
What about a toothbrush ?
[ SIGHS ]
Voodoo .
Right , we 've gotta find flashlights ,
torches , guns , whatever the fuck they got on this island , so we can get off .
What if he 's down there collecting body parts or something ?
Let 's just get the fuck out of here , all right ?
WILL : You guys should just wait right here .
KARLA : No , why can 't we come with you ?
' Cause it 's safer here , all right ?
Just be a second .
One second .
[ THUNDER CLAPS ]
Julie , where you goin ' ?
[ ELECTRICAL BANGS ]
Ooh , what the hell was that ?
Shit . Julie ?
Brasilia .
[ GASPS ]
Julie , watch out !
That 's the capital of Brazil .
Not Rio .
[ PANTS ]
[ PANICKED SHOUTS ]
Get away from her , you crazy motherfucker !
Leave him alone !
- This is the killer ! - No !
Bullshit , we 've seen the voodoo stuff .
No . I found the bodies this morning .
I tried to use the radio , but he had already destroyed it .
- Leave him alone , I believe him . - Come on , Julie , you saw his room !
I haven 't hurt anyone . I stole those things to help you ...
to protect you .
He could have easily killed me , but he didn 't .
Jesus Christ , we didn 't even answer the radio question right !
This whole thing was a setup .
- What the fuck are you talking about ? - Rio isn 't the capital of Brazil !
Sorry , wrong answer ! We lose .
So , then where is he , huh ?
- Where 's this Ben Willis guy , huh ? - I don 't know .
You never fucking know !
I mean , what , we 're supposed to just trust you , huh ?
How do we know you ain 't the one who set this whole thing up ?
Yeah , how do we know that you 're not ?
I know who you 're talking about .
He used to work here at the hotel .
Lately , I 've seen him out in the woods , by the orchard .
- If you like , I can show you . - How do we know he 's not setting us up ?
- Where else are you gonna go ? - All I know is , I 'm not staying here .
We 're gonna be better off in the open and if we stick together ,
maybe we can kill this asshole for good .
Show us .
[ THUNDER CLAPS ]
[ BOATS RATTLE ]
[ STATIC ]
[ TV PLAYS ]
[ DOOR CREAKS ]
What the hell ?
I need to get to Tower Bay island .
- We 're closed . - I need to get to that island now .
Let me ask you somethin ' , sport .
Did you happen to see what it 's like outside ?
[ GUN COCKS ]
I 'm not looking for a weather report .
I 'm looking for a boat .
So which one 's yours ?
ESTES : He worked here for many years .
Raised a family , pretty wife ,
two little ones ; a boy and a girl .
One day , the wife went missing .
Maid found blood all over the honeymoon suite , room 201 .
Eventually , they found the body ... pieces of it , at least .
People say she was cheating on him .
People say he would beat her .
People say a lot of things .
He disappeared ...
children too .
Now , he 's back .
KARLA : Julie , be careful . JULIE : I 've gotta see .
[ SIGHS ]
[ THUNDER CLAPS ]
What 's today 's date ?
July 4th .
I 'm not gonna die on this island !
Do you hear me ?
If you want me , Ben , come and get me !
I 'm right here but my grave stays empty !
Julie , this is crazy , all right ?
The phone lines are down and the boats are gone ,
and there 's no way off this island .
Yeah , then we fight .
Where did Estes go ?
Why , Will ? He can 't help us anyway .
He 's probably the only one who can .
[ GROANS ]
- I 'll find him . - I 'm goin ' with you .
Are you crazy ? You 're gonna leave us here by ourselves ?
It 's okay , he couldn 't have gone far . I 'll catch up with you guys later .
- No ! - No , Will !
- Meet us back at the hotel , okay ! - Damn it !
Come on , let 's go !
[ STORM RAGES ]
[ DRAW CLAN KS ]
Yes .
[ KNIFE CHINKS ]
[ TY PANTS ]
See what I really need is a gun , not a knife .
So , what 's up ?
What are you gonna do with those ? You gonna butter him ?
You gonna clean vegetables ?
[ SIGHS ]
Take this .
- You ready ? - Yeah .
Shit . Hey . Hey .
You okay ?
We 're gonna get this fucker , right ?
Right ?
- Right , let 's head to the pantry . - Why , is that a good place to hide ?
I don 't know . I 'm just fucking hungry .
WILL : Hey ! Estes , Where 'd you go ?
What the fuck , man , you said you were gonna help us !
You should 've told us you had a boat .
[ THUNDER CLAPS ]
- We 're not going anywhere . - What ?
[ THUD ]
[ DOOR CREAKS AND THUDS ]
Baby , don 't go in here .
It 's only food , don 't even worry about it , baby .
It 's only food .
Stop trying to act like you ain 't hungry .
[ SIGHS ]
[ THUMPS ]
[ HEAVY BREATHING ]
[ CLATTERS ]
TY : Shit !
[ SCREAMS ]
It 's just a stupid rat .
[ GRUNTS ]
[ SCREAMS ]
No , Nancy !
[ STORM RAGES ]
[ INDISTINCT 0.5 . RADIO ]
Come in ! Come in !
Come on !
[ BEEPS ]
Come in . This is the Arcadian requesting emergency assistance ...
for Tower Bay island .
I repeat . This is the Arcadian requesting emergency assistance .
[ BEEPS AND STATIC ]
[ BEEPS ]
JULIE : So , that 's where the flashlights were .
[ TY SCOFFS ]
Look , I 'm sorry , but you could have been the one doing all this .
And so could you , crazy bitch .
Hey , you 're the one who broke into my hiding place !
I 'm sorry . I must have missed the sign .
Excuse me , but this place didn 't have a murder rate until you people showed up !
[ SIGHS ]
I 've never seen a dead body before .
Yeah , get used to it .
- Who 's doing this ? - TY : Boy , here we go .
Look , don 't even get her started , all right ?
It 's a long , fucked up story .
You probably won 't believe a word of it anyway .
All I know is that this is the worst vacation of my whole life .
I 'm tired , I 'm hungry , I 'm fucking horny and personally ,
I haven 't seen one god damn psycho killer .
[ GROANS ]
[ SCREAMS ]
[ GROANS AND GURGLES ]
Ty !
[ CRASH ]
- Run ! Run ! Come on ! - Where do we run ?
Run ! Come on !
[ RUNNING FOOTSTEPS ]
[ THUNDER CLAPS ]
[ KNIFE CHINKS ]
[ SCREAMS ]
Come on . Karla , come on .
[ PANTING ]
JULIE : Karla ! Karla !
[ SCREAMS ]
Oh shit . It won 't look !
Shit !
NANCY : Follow me . Stay on the beams .
[ THUMPING FOOTSTEPS ]
[ banging on door ]
Jesus Christ , that 's my bedroom !
[ KARLA SCREAMS ]
No !
[ SCREAMS ]
Come on , give me your hand !
Come on ! Come on !
NANCY : Come on ! Come on !
Come on !
God , you sick freak !
- Come on ! - KARLA : No !
Come on , Karla !
Karla !
[ SCREAMS ]
[ SMASH ]
BOTH : Karla !
[ PANTING ]
Shit ! Shit !
[ HOOK SWIPES ]
[ SCREAMS ]
Shit ! We 've got to do something !
No , she is never gonna make it ! Come on !
Get off me !
- [ NANCY GROANS ] - Shit !
[ STORM RAGES ]
Holy shit .
[ PANTS ]
[ GLASS CRACKING ] [ WINCES ]
[ CRACKING GLASS ]
Oh shit ...
[ SCREAMS ]
[ PETRIFIED SCREAMS ]
[ SMASH ]
[ HEAVY BREATHING ]
[ BIRDS FLAPPING ]
[ GROANS ]
[ THUNDER CLAPS ]
[ BROKEN GLASS RATTLES ]
[ BIRDS FLAP ]
[ GROANS ]
Damn , it 's locked .
[ FOOTSTEPS ]
- Are you okay ? - I 'll live .
It 's locked .
[ CHAIN RATTLES ]
NANCY : We 've got to open the door .
We 're gonna get you out of here , I promise . I promise .
- It 's one of these . Sorry . - Come on !
[ NANCY GROANS ]
Karla !
[ KARLA SCREAMS ]
Shit ! Come on , open the door !
Come on !
[ HOOK CHINKS ]
- Help me ! - JULIE : Nancy !
[ FOOTSTEPS ]
Come on , Nancy , Open the door !
Come on !
- The key ... I can 't find it ! - Come on !
Get out of the way !
[ SMASH ]
[ SHOUTS ]
JULIE : Karla , come on !
Come on , Karla !
[ GROANS ]
[ SCREAMS ]
Shit !
- JULIE : Where are we going ? - NANCY : The storm shelter !
[ STORM RAGES ]
[ PANTS ]
Don 't worry , I know there 's emergency power here somewhere .
- Hey , Julie ? - Karla , just grab a hold of my hand .
- Hey , Julie ? - Karla , just grab a hold of my hand !
I am holding your hand !
No , you 're not .
[ ELECTRICITY BUZZES ]
[ EVERYBODY SCREAMS ]
[ EVERYBODY SCREAMS AGAIN ]
[ THUDDING FOOTSTEPS ]
You guys okay ?
- Oh , my god , it 's Will ! - Come on , let 's get outta here .
[ PANTS ]
Come on ! Come on !
Everything 's gonna be okay , let 's just get inside .
- Did you get help ? What happened ? - Estes attacked me !
JULIE : What ? Wait , you think he 's a part of this ?
- I don 't know ! - Your stomach . You 're hurt .
I 'll be okay . Let 's just get inside .
Wait a minute . I don 't think we should go inside .
Look , the last time I saw the " slicker guy " was on the beach .
I think we 're safe , okay ?
[ PANTING ]
JULIE : Jesus , you 're bleeding to death .
We need to find a first aid kit .
I think there 's one in the lobby .
- Okay , just sit there . - Oh .
Don 't worry , he 's gone . Just go , it 'll be okay .
Look , I 'll go with you . Come on .
Come on .
Listen , Will , you 're gonna be okay , all right ?
Jesus , there 's blood everywhere .
[ GROANS ]
I can 't find a wound .
That 's because it 's not my blood .
What ?
It 's not my blood , Julie .
[ THUNDER CLAPS ]
What 's your favorite radio station , Julie ?
[ WHIMPERS ]
[ SCREAMS ]
Come on , Julie , what 's your favorite radio station ?
- No ...
96.7 . It 's time for you to contemplate the ultimate quickie getaway .
[ SOBS ]
No !
[ SCREAMS ]
[ DRAWS OPEN AND CLOSE ]
Oh , here . Take that .
Come on ! Come on !
[ KARLA SCREAMS ]
Estes !
[ GIRLS PANT ]
Fuck !
[ GROANS ]
[ SQUELCHING THUD ]
Get off me !
Get up !
God , no !
[ GROANS ]
[ SCREAMS ]
[ CHOKES ]
[ SMASH ]
I mean , look at the bright side , Jules .
We finally get to spend some quality time together .
- Why are you doing this to me ? - Me , me , me . It 's always about you .
" I 'm having bad dreams . I can 't sleep . I 'm not doing well in school .
- I 'm having trouble with my boyfriend . " - But I trusted you .
Oh , you are so much like the rest of them !
You never take responsibility for anything you do ,
and you think you can get away with murder !
[ GROANS ]
What 'd you do that for ?
You 're a bitch .
[ GROANS ]
Hmm . That 's gonna leave a mark .
- Just tell me why ! - Why ? Come on , Jules , think about it !
You 'll get it ! Will Benson !
Ben 's son !
Hi , dad .
[ JULIE CRIES ]
No .
[ SHRIEKS ]
Hush , now .
No more screaming .
No more running .
It 's time to die !
RAY : Let her go !
[ GUN COCKS ]
Let her go .
Oh , you 've gotta be shittin ' me .
What are you gonna do , boy , call us names ?
Let her go , now !
Think about it , boy .
You 're no killer . That 's my job .
You don 't have it in you .
[ THUNDER CLAPS ]
[ GUN CLICKS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ CRUNCH ]
[ THUDS AND GRUNTS ]
[ GROWLS AND YELLS ]
[ SPITS ]
Sure did miss you down here , Ray !
It 's too bad . We could have been friends !
I mean really , man ! I would have shared her with you !
Come on , Ray , stay with me . You see that ?
Now , I want you to think about all the things we 're gonna do to her !
You want him , dad ?
Stand him up .
[ GROANS ]
[ CHOKES ]
[ THUD ]
[ YELLS ]
[ GUNSHOTS ]
Just "
fucking ... die !
[ GUN CLICKS ]
[ BIRDS TWITTER ]
[ WAVES CRASH ]
[ HELICOPTER APPROACHES ]
P.A. : This is the coast guard !
Remain where you are !
The rescue team will be with you shortly !
KARLA : Julie ?
Karla .
Karla , god , I thought I would never see you again .
Oh , girl , you don 't have to worry about me .
I 'm made of steel .
[ SIGHS ]
Good old Ray , huh ?
Hey , Karla .
[ HELICOPTER WHIRS ]
If anyone asks , let 's not tell them it rained the whole time , okay ?
It 'll be our little secret .
Yeah .
JULIE : Hey , I almost fell asleep on the couch .
You didn 't tell me how late it was .
[ CHUCKLES ]
- Were you checking the locks again ? - Oh , you know me too well .
Don 't you dare go to sleep , girl .
[ CHUCKLES ]
[ DOG BARKS ]
[ THUMPING ]
Ray ?
[ TOOTHBRUSH BUZZES ]
I love this thing .
[ WATER RUNS ]
[ SPITS ]
[ WIND HOWLS ]
[ CLOTHES HANGERS RATTLE ]
[ FOOTSTEPS ]
Julie , what the hell is your problem ?
Just ... stop .
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
[ JINGLES ]
[ SCREAMS ]
♪ If I should die this very moment ♪
♪ I wouldn 't fear ♪
♪ For I 've never known completeness ♪
♪ Like being here ♪
♪ All this time I 've loved you ♪
♪ And never known your face ♪
♪ All this time I 've missed you ♪
♪ And searched this human race ♪
♪ I 've found the one ♪
♪ I 've waited for ♪
♪ The one I 've waited for ♪
♪ Wanna stay right here ♪
♪ Till the end of time ♪
♪ Till the earth stops turning ♪
♪ Gonna love you till the seas run dry ♪
♪ I 've found the one ♪
♪ I 've waited for ♪
♪ The one ♪
♪ Wanna stay right here ♪
♪ Till the end of time ♪
♪ Till the earth stops turning ♪
♪ Gonna love you till the seas run dry ♪
♪ I 've found the one ♪
♪ I 've waited for ♪
♪ The one ♪